KENYAN NAGY

Halifax, Nova Scotia Phone: (250) 299-8871

Email: Kenyan.nagy@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Bilingual customer service expert with eleven years' experience working in the hospitality industry while completing studies on a full-time basis. Areas of expertise, skills and competencies include:

Customer Service Administration
Logistics Planning Time Management

Detail-oriented Efficient

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Lord Nelson Hotel and Suites

April 2018 - Present

- Concierge
 - Experience in a highly professional and confidential atmosphere, responsible for the care of high-profile and celebrity guests
 - Organized and detail-oriented, planned logistics for guests across Atlantic Canada
 - Efficient and capable, execute calm and professional "just-in-time" delivery of large parties on a weekly basis

The Grawood

September 2016 - May 2019

Bartender

- Coordinated logistics for multiple off-site events involving food and beverage
- Responsibly served hundreds of attendees at various events from formal galas to sports tournaments
- Organized and tracked inventory and cash flow

Dairyland Foods

June 2008 – August 2015

Associate

- Responsible for customer engagement and satisfaction, worked with 50 clients on an annual basis
- Experienced administrator, handled merchandising, invoicing as well as start and end of day reporting
- Strong salesman, consistently ensured a high inventory turnover rate, limiting product waste

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts Major in Political Science Completing on a part-time basis Dalhousie University 2015 - Present

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Customer engagement and building strong relationships;

On-the-job experience in scoping, coordination and administration;

Software competencies: Microsoft Suite products including Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Outlook; social media.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Kamloops District School Board Volunteer	2009 - 2013
Westsyde Secondary School Rugby Team Captain	2013 - 2014
Kamloops Wildfire Relief Centre Volunteer	2016
Kamloops Golf & Country Club Line Cook	2017
The Muse Café & Pub Bartender	2017 - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

British Columbia Food Safety Level 1 Forklift Operators Class 3 – Handtrucks, Power-jacks Nova Scotia Safe Serve

REFERENCES

Available upon request.